Yui!
唯
あッ 和ちゃん
Hi, Nodoka.
Wanna walk home with me?
一緒に帰ろ
Oh, no, I'm sorry, Nodoka. There's a club meeting I have to go to today.
ごめ～ん 今日どうしても部活に行かなきゃいけないんだ
Oh, really? I guess I'll have to walk by myself.
そうなんだ それじゃあ仕方ないね
She's finally found something she can get into.
唯にも 打ち込めるものができたのね
I'm happy and sad at the same time.
うれしいよう 悲しいような…
What's wrong, Yui?
どうしたの？
Mugi-chan said she's gonna bring some tasty snacks today!
今日はムギちゃん おいしいお菓子持ってきてくれるんだ
You're not going to play guitar?
ギターやるんじゃないの？
It was like this even in kindergarten,
幼稚園のときも
and in grade school, too.
小学生のときも
Even when we got into middle school.
中学生になっても ずっと ボーッと生きてきたけど
アイス…
Your ice cream.
My life's always been kinda unfocused.
And now that I finally made it to high school.
高校生になった私は初めて…
I've joined a club for the first time!
部活を始めました！
Chatting Now
TRIPPIN' OUT
ガチでカシマシ　Never Ending Girls' Talk
It's really noisy
Never ending girls talk
I can't wait until the bell
rings at the end of class
終業チャイムまで待てない
遅刻はしても早退はNon Non Non!
Even if I'm late,
leaving early is a
No no!
精一杯Study After School
study
hard
I'll
after
School
ドキドキが止まんない　フルスロットルな脳内
My heart won't stop thumping
Why is it going on full throttle?
希望·欲望·煩悩　リボンかけて包装
Hope
Desire
Suffering
Wrap them all up with a ribbon
ネタどっさり持ち寄り　New　Type　Version打ち込み
I'll gather lots of data
and I'll put it all in a new type
男子禁制のプリ帳　恋綴った日記帳
I have a photo album without guys
and a diary written with love
スカート丈2cm　詰めたら跳ぶよ
If I cut my skirt
by 2 centimeters,
I can fly
昨日より遠く　おとといよりオクターブ高く
Further than yesterday,
I'll reach a higher octave
than the day before
Jumping Now
Jumping
out
ガチでウルワシ　Never Ending Girls' Life
It's beautiful
Never ending
girls life
日々マジ　ライブだし待ったなし
I'm looking
forward
to the daily
concert
早起きしても早寝はNon Non Non!
Even if I
get up early,
going to bed
early is a
No no!
目一杯Shouting　わっしょい
Fight with all
W
e've
got
Hooray
It's splendid
ガチでスバラシ　Never Ending Girls' Song
Never ending
Girls talk
午後ティータイムには持ってこい
The afternoon
tea  time
is perfect
My unrequited
L
O
V
E
will be defeated
片思いでも玉砕でHere we go!
But here I go!
歌えばShining After School
I'll
sing
for
you
After school
Sign: Preparation Room
Hey, everyone!
こんにちは
These three are my fellow Light Music Club members.
この３人が軽音部の仲間です
よッ
Hello.
こんにちは
This is Mio Akiyama, our bassist.
ベース担当の…秋山 澪ちゃん
She's tall and pretty, and gives off a real "cool grown woman" vibe.
背が高くて かっこいい 大人の女性って感じです
Hey, Mio. How come you decided to take up playing bass instead of a regular guitar?
ねえねえ 何で澪ちゃんは
ギターじゃなくて ベースをやろうと思ったの？
Playing guitar is... well, embarrassing.
だってギターは…
はッ はずかしい
E-Embarrassing?!
はずかしい!?
You know, the guitar is the core instrument of the band, and because of that, you have to play right up in front of the group.
ギターって バンドの中心って感じで
先頭に立って演奏しなきゃいけないし
So the eyes of everyone in the audience are on you.
観客の目も 自然と集まるだろ？
Just thinking about being in a position like that makes me...
自分が その立場になるって考えただけで…
Mio!
澪ちゃん！？
Mio is kinda delicate.
澪ちゃんは 少し繊細です
Mio, are you all right?
大丈夫？
This is our keyboardist, Tsumugi Kotobuki.
キーボード担当…琴吹 紬ちゃん
We call her Mugi for short. She's calm, soothing, and really really nice.
通称 ムギちゃん
おっとり ぽわぽわ かわいい人です
You know, you're a terrific keyboard player, Mugi. I bet you've been playing for a long time.
ムギちゃんは キーボードうまいよね
キーボード歴 長いの？
I started studying the piano when I was only four years old.
私 ４歳のころからピアノを習ってたの
I've been managed to win a few awards at some competitions.
コンクールで賞をもらったこともあるのよ
へッ へえ～ すごいね！
Wow! That's amazing!
Why did she join the Light Music Club?
何で軽音部にいるんだろう
All right. Dig in, everyone!
さあ いただきましょう
Oh, I almost forgot, I've been meaning to ask you something.
そういえば ずっと疑問に思ってたんだけど
This club room is really nice and very well equipped.
この部室って やけに物がそろってるよね
Are all of the high schools in this area like this nowadays?
最近の高校って こんな感じなのかな
Oh, no. I brought all that stuff from my house.
ああ それは 私のウチから持ってきたのよ
It's yours?!
自前!?
Yes.
はい
Mugi is definitely one of those "rich girl" types.
ムギちゃんは かなり お嬢様っぽいです
Our drummer's name is Ritsu Tainaka.
ドラム担当の…田井中 律ちゃん
She's a cheerful girl who's just full of energy.
元気いっぱいの 明るい女の子です
You really seem like someone who would be a drummer.
りっちゃんは ドラム～って感じだよね
What?!
…んな！？
I've got a completely legitimate reason for that. A powerful reason that moves almost everyone who hears it!
私にもちゃんと すごく立派な
聞けば誰でも感動する理由があるんだぞ！
What? Tell me, tell me, come on!
へえ～ どんな どんな？
It's because...
それは え～っと あれだ…
Well, you know it's... 'Cause they're cool.
…カッコイイから
That's it?
そこ？
Oh, come on!
だってさ
Just imagining you're having to wriggle my fingers like crazy just to play a guitar, bass, or keyboard makes me wanna scream!
ギターとか ベースとか キーボードとか
指で ちまちま ちまちまするのを 想像しただけで…
キーーッ！ って なるんだよ
I... really hate it.
Wow, I guess your choice of instruments reflects your personality.
楽器選びにも 性格が出るんだな
Instrument!
Would you like another one?
おかわりはいかが？
Yes, thank you!
ありがとう
So you first wanted to join the Choir Club, but joined ours instead?
そういえば ムギちゃんは 合唱部に入りたかったんでしょ？
That's right. You see, I wanted to pick a club where I could make friends with sort of fun, pleasant people that one so rarely meets.
ええ でも めったに出会えない
とっても楽しくて 愉快な人達の仲間になりたかったの
We're like rare animals to her?
珍獣ってことですか…
That reminds me, Miss Hirasawa, have you bought your guitar yet?
そういえば平沢さん もうギターは買ったの？
Just call me Yui.
唯でいいよ
After all, I already call you by your first name, right, Mio?
私 すでに澪ちゃんのこと「澪ちゃん」って呼んでるし
Y-Yui?
ゆ… ゆい？
That's so cute!
かッ かわいい
So, what about your guitar, Yui?
で 唯 ギターは？
Guitar?
ギター？
Oh, yeah, that's right! I forgot. I'm supposed to play guitar, aren't I?
あッ そっか 忘れてた
私 ギターやるんだっけ
Yeah, well, this IS the Light Music Club.
軽音部は喫茶店じゃないぞ
Do you know how much guitars are gonna cost? A lot?
ギターって どれぐらいするの？ 値段
う～ん 安いのは１万円代からあるけど
Well, the cheap ones start way down in the low hundreds, but believe me you really don't want one that's too cheap.
あんまり安すぎるのも よくないからな
Something around $500 should be fine.
５万円くらいが いいかも
That much?!
５万？ 私のお小遣い 10ヵ月分…
$500 is ten months' allowance.
Yeah well, expensive guitars can run up into the thousands.
高いのは10万円以上するのもあるよ
Can I use club funds?
部費で落ちませんか？
Nothing doing!
落ちません～
Here, try one, they're delicious.
これ おいしいわよ
Anyway, we can't really do anything if you don't have an instrument.
とにかく 楽器がないと 何も始まらないしな
Right, then. Let's go check out guitars on our next day off!
よ～し 今度の休みに ギター見に行こうぜ
Go!
'Tis vexing...
無念なり…
Yes?
Hey, come on, Sis. Dinner's ready.
お姉ちゃん ごはんだよ
Oh, Ui...
憂…
What's wrong, Big Sis?
どうしたの？
I joined the Light Music Club.
軽音部に入ったの
Really?
So, I wanna buy a guitar I can use.
でね ギター買いたいんだけど…
I didn't even know you could play the guitar!
お姉ちゃん ギター弾けたんだ
ううん 全然
I can't!
So anyway, you think maybe you could lend me some money, I'll pay you back.
でね… お金を貸していただけないでしょうか
I'm sorry, but I don't have a whole lot of money either.
ごめんね 私もあんまりない…
Yeah, I figured...
ですよね～
Hey, why don't you just ask Mom for an advance on your allowance?
お母さんに お小遣いの前借り 頼んでみたら？
I'll even go with you if you want me to, to back you up.
私も一緒に お願いしてあげる
Oh, Little Sis. I can always count on you!
さすが～ 頼りになる！
Yui, hey! Over here! Over here!
唯 こっちこっち
Oh, hey, guys!
あッ みんな
痛ッ
Sorry!
ごめんなさい！
She's got like ten feet left.
あと数メートルなのに…
But she can't make it the rest of the way?
たどり着けない!?
Who's a good boy?
Who's a good doggie?
あッ しゃしゃしゃしゃ～
Did the money situation work out?
お金は大丈夫だった？
I begged my mom and I got her to give me a $500 advance on my allowance.
お母さんに無理言って ５万円 前借りさせてもらった
I have to be real careful with my spending from now on...
これからは計画的に使わなきゃ…
And make sure I don't waste money...
いけないんだけど…
I can buy this now!
今なら買える
Come on, Yui!
こらこら
Oh, I'm just looking.
ちょっと見るだけ
ああ～ 疲れた
Boy, I'm exhausted.
I stocked up!
買っちった～
Wow, this was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
楽しかったですね
So, where do you guys wanna go next? Wait a sec. Are we forgetting something?
次 どこ行こうか
あれ… 何か忘れてない？
Your instrument, dummy!
楽器だ 楽器
Whoa, geez. I forgot!
おおッ しまった
Oh, wow!
すご～い
Look at all the guitars!
ギターが いっぱい
Hey, hey!
Yui! See anything that you like?
唯 どれがいいか決めた？
Are there guidelines or something to choose by?
何か 選ぶ基準とか あるのかな
Of course there are.
もちろんあるよ
There's the tone of the guitar, of course.
ギターって 音色はもちろん
But there's also its weight, composition, and the shape and thickness of the neck.
重さや ネックの形や太さも いろいろあるんだ
So for girls, one with a slender neck would be...
だから女の子は ネックが細いほうが…
あッ このギター かわいい
This guitar here is cute!
She never listens!
聞いちゃいねえ
That guitar costs $2,500.
そのギター 25万円もするぞ
あッ ホントだ…
Wow, it does. Oh, that's way, way more than I can afford.
これは さすがに手が出ないや…
Do you have your heart set on this one?
このギターが欲しいの？
うん
There's some cheap ones over there.
あっちに安いのあるぜ
I really want this one, though...
やっぱ これがいいな…
This reminds me how badly I wanted my current bass. I agonized over it.
そういえば
私も今のベースが欲しくて 悩んで 悩んで
I-I'd like this one!
こッ これください！
And I haggled like crazy when I bought my used drum set.
私も 中古のドラムセット 値切って 値切って
You can do better! No, try again!
もうひと声 もうひと声～
You made the salesman cry.
店員さん 泣いてたぞ
Yeah, well, I wasn't leaving the store without those drums.
どうしても あのドラムが欲しかったんだよ
Um, what is "haggling"?
あの 値切るって？
It's when you use grift and determination to force someone to lower the price on something you really want!
欲しいものを手に入れるために
努力と根性でまけさせることだよ
That is amazing! It's almost admirable!
すごいですね 何か あこがれます
What's so admirable about it?
あこがれる要素が どこに…
Yui...
…唯
Got it! Let's all get a temp job!
よ～し みんなでバイトしよう
Temp job?
バイト？
Mm-hm. So we can help Yui buy her guitar!
うん 唯の楽器を買うために
えッ そッ そんな悪いよ
No, I can't let you do that!
Don't sweat it! This will be a club activity!
これも軽音部の活動の一環だって
Oh, Ritchan...
りっちゃん
I'll try it! It could be fun!
私 やってみたいです
Mugi-chan?
ムギちゃん
All right! Let's get to it!
よっしゃ やるぞ～
Go!
Go! Wow, wow!
What kind of job are we talking about?
…どんなバイトするんだろう
けいおん！
A job?
バイト？
Yes, so I can buy a guitar!
うん ギター買うために
When did she become so self-sufficient? I'm happy and sad at the same time.
いつの間に こんな自立した子に
うれしいような 悲しいような…
The rest of the Light Music Club have offered to help me get it.
軽音部のみんなも 協力してくれるんだ
What? You've got the others involved?
えッ みんなを巻き込んで？
Yeah!
うん
So, what kind of job should we be looking for?
何のバイトがいいかな
We could hand out packs of tissues.
ティッシュを配るのは？
I-I can't...
むッ 無理
What about a job in fast food?
ファーストフードは どうですか？
Welcome, can I take your order?
い… いらっしゃい…ましぇ
That's the problem.
ダメ かも
Oh, right. Might be kind of tough hurdle for you, Mio.
そっか 澪にはハードル高いかもね
I couldn't push the button if I thought somebody scary would answer.
怖い人が出てきたらと思うと 玄関のベルが押せない
I can't go and take orders!
オーダーが聞きにいけない
Miss Mio!
みッ 澪さん
Oh, please don't push yourself on my account!
ごめんね 無理しなくていいから
I keep telling myself I can't do it before I even try.
やる前から無理だとか ダメだとかばかり言ってる
This is so Yui can buy a guitar!
唯のギターを買うためなのに
So it's for the greater good of the Light Music Club!
それは軽音部のためでもあるのに
I have to overcome my limitations!
乗り越えないと 自分を
私 何でもやるよ
Name the job! I'll do anything!
W-What is it?
なッ 何!?
How about this?
これなんて どう？
"Traffic Volume Survey"?
交通量調査
We have to count the number of people and cars that pass by us. We do it using a counter.
歩いてる人や 車の数を数えるんだよ
カウンターを持って
Like the Wild Bird Society!
あッ 野鳥の会？
This is a job even Mio can do!
これなら澪も できるっしょ
Yes, you're right!
ホントですね
See you later!
行ってきま～す
Wait, Sis! Don't forget your lunch!
あッ お姉ちゃん お弁当
Why so much?
こんなに!?
I made lunch for everyone else in the Light Music Club, too.
軽音部のみなさんの分も用意したの
I mean after all they took this job to help you, right?
お姉ちゃんのために バイトしてくれるんでしょ？
Yeah! Thanks, Ui!
わ～い ありがとう
Here.
ほい
Now, we'll work in pairs and trade off every hour.
２人ずつ １時間ごとに交代だから
Goodness, you're very nimble.
軽快ですね
Oh, yeah.
えいや～
ほお～ こしゃくな
Looks like a challenge.
You're really fast, Ritchan!
りっちゃん 速～い
痛いッ
Finger cramped!
つった…
That happens when you get worked up.
ムキになるからだ
You know, we have a bit of time before the survey starts.
調査開始まで あとちょっと ありますね
I think we should all four have some tea.
とりあえず お茶にしましょう
Yeah, let's go have a picnic!
わあ～ ピクニック
You guys really worry me sometimes.
あッ みんな 何だか心配だ
This weather sure feels nice today, doesn't it, Mugi?
天気がよくて 気持ちいいね
Yes, it does.
そうね
She is like a highlands princess!
高原のお嬢様？
A magazine giveaway?
雑誌の懸賞？
One of the prizes is a guitar.
賞品は ギターだって
That might just be the fastest way to get it, all right.
確かに こっちのほうが早いかもな
Could be.
だろ？
Mugi, aren't you tired at all?
ムギちゃん 疲れない？
No, I feel fine.
大丈夫よ
Then, your thumb doesn't hurt, either?
指 痛くない？
うん
Uh-uh.
You aren't sleepy?
眠くない？
I just pressed the button on the counter instead of answering you!
返事する代わりに カウンター押しちゃった…
She's playing a four beat.
今のは フォービート
And that's an eight beat.
今のは エイトビート
Keep your mind on the job!
って マジメにやれ！
Mugi, these sweets are really great and all,
ムギちゃん すごくおいしいんだけど
but is it okay for us to keep eating this fancy food all the time?
こんな高そうなお菓子
いつももらっちゃって いいのかな
Oh, it's fine.
いいのよ いつもいろんな方から いただくんだけど
All sorts of people give me these all the time.
If I left them at home, it would only go to waste.
家に置いていても 余らせてしまうから
People bring your family enough sweets to go to waste? What kind of family are you?!
いろんな人から 余るほどお菓子をもらう家って どんな家？
I'm counting the clouds.
流れる雲を数えてる
Is this an occupational sickness?
これって職業病!?
That's a wrap for day one!
１日目 終了
Well, I'll be out for the station, then.
じゃあ 私は駅へ行くから
Mio and I are going by bus.
私と澪はバス
You said that you're walking home, right, Yui?
唯は歩いて帰るんだっけ？
Mm-hm.
うん
Tomorrow, let's--
明日も…
Yeah! Let's eat some more those great sweets!
うん お菓子よろしく～
I was going to say, "Tomorrow, let's all work hard again."
頑張りましょうって 言おうとしたんだけど
Yeah...
You better watch it!
こらこら
But if they'll just go to waste then...
でも 余ってるんだったら…
Watch it! Watch it! Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it.
こらこらこら こらこらこら…
It is an occupational sickness...
やっぱり職業病だ
Bye, see ya!
じゃあね
Sure.
バイバイ
Bye! See you tomorrow.
また明日
Hey, guys!
みんな～
Thanks for everything, I mean it!
ホントに ありがとね
I promise, when I finally get my guitar, I'm gonna practice every day!
私 ギター買ったら
毎日 練習するね
Thank you for two days of hard work.
２日間 お疲れさま
Ma'am, the pleasure was all ours!
お世話になりました
Here.
はい
So, $80 per day, huh?
１日 ８千円か
Even with the $500 advance your mother gave you, that's still nowhere near enough.
お母さんに前借りした５万円と合わせても
まだ全然たりないわね
Guess we have to work a few more jobs, then.
あと何回か バイトするか
You're right, Miss Mio.
そうですね
Okay. Guess I'll hit the want ads again.
よし じゃあ また探そっか
Right!
うん
I just can't take this money from you.
やっぱりこれ いいよ
Please, I want you to spend the money that you earned on yourselves.
バイト代は みんな自分のために使って
But, Yui...
唯ちゃん…
I'll buy myself a guitar all on my own.
私 自分で買えるギターを買う
Yui...
唯…
I wanna get a guitar and start practicing right away so I can play with you guys.
１日でも早く練習して みんなと一緒に演奏したいもん
Would you mind going out to the music store with me again tomorrow?
また 楽器屋さんにつきあってもらってもいい？
うん
Thanks for everything, guys. I'd better go home now.
みんな ありがとう じゃあ帰るね
うん また明日
See you tomorrow, Yui.
Good bye.
じゃあね
Bye, guys.
I have to get good fast for me and for them.
みんなのためにも 早く うまくならなきゃ
Well, I'd best be heading home, too.
じゃあ 私も帰るわね
うん
Oh, man, I think Yui's losing it.
何か 恥ずかしい人になってるぞ
あッ…
She really wants that badly.
よっぽど 欲しいんだな
Okay, then let's get another job!
よっしゃ やっぱ またバイトを…
Wait right here, okay?
ちょっと待ってて
Hi, excuse me.
あの
Yes?
はい
Would you mind terribly if I haggled?
値切ってもいいですか？
Huh?
はあ？
Could you see your way to lowering the price on a guitar?
ギターのお値段 まけてもらえないでしょうか？
Y-You're the company president's daughter!
あなたは… 社長の娘さん!?
Perhaps... I could go this low?
では こんなもんで
もうひと声～
No, try again!
He says that he will sell you this guitar for $500.
このギター ５万円で売ってくれるって
Serious?!
マジで!?
What?! What did you say to him?
何 何やったの!?
The thing is, this store is my family's business consortium.
このお店 実はウチの系列のお店で
Oh.
Really, is that so? Wow...
そ そうなんだ…
Mugi, I don't know how to thank you. I'll pay you back the rest, I promise!
ムギちゃん ありがとう
残りは ちゃんと返すから
えへへ～ かわいいな～
It's so cute!
Bowrrm!
I look like a rocker!
ミュージシャンっぽい！
あッ サインの練習しなきゃ！
I gotta practice signing my autograph!
Big Sis, could you keep it down...
お姉ちゃん うるさい
Hey Sis, if you don't get up soon, you'll be late for school!
お姉ちゃん 早く起きないと遅刻するよ
Big Sister?
お姉ちゃん？
She slept with it...
添い寝
Awesome!
すっげ～
Wow, the guitar looks like it belongs on you.
ギター持つと それらしく見えるね
Try playing something!
何か 弾いてみて
You really haven't practiced at all yet, have you?
まだ 全然 練習してないの？
Well, the guitar is all bright and shiny and new and everything. And I guess I'm just a little scared to touch it.
いや～ だってギターって キラキラ ピカピカしてるから
何か 触るのが怖くて
Yeah, I can totally relate to that.
ああ わかる わかる
I posed in front of the mirror with it, and took a lot of pictures of it, and slept all night with it, though.
鏡の前で ポーズとったり 写真撮ったり
添い寝したりは したんだけど
So, play it.
弾けよ
You haven't even taken the film off of it yet.
そういや ギターのフィルムも 外してないもんね
I couldn't help myself!
なんちって～
Ritsu, apologize!
律 謝れ！
I'm sorry! I acted on impulse! Please forgive me!
ごめん ほんの出来心だったんだ
ごめんね 唯ちゃん
Here, why don't you have a snack.
唯ちゃん お菓子 お菓子
Oh, something like that won't--
そんなもので機嫌が… 直った！
It made her feel better!
No, you're right. The purpose of guitar is to be played by someone.
そうだよね ギターって やっぱり弾くものだよね
And so it's not right to just sit and admire it and never use it.
ただ大事にしてるだけじゃ かわいそうだよね
Thanks for that, Ritsu. I really needed that motivation.
ありがとう りっちゃん
私 やる気出てきた
It was?! Well, I was kinda hoping it would give you the urge to practice.
そうか？
唯が練習する きっかけになればと思ったんだ
Boy, I'm good... Ow!
さすが… 痛ッ
So, shall we practice, then?
じゃあ 練習するか
How do I get the guitar to sound like they're doing in a concert?
ライブみたいな音出すのは どうしたらいいのかな
You just gotta hook it up to an amp.
アンプにつないだら出るよ
Ready!
よし
That was awesome!
かっこいい
It's finally started.
やっとスタートだな
We've got our Light Music Club.
私達の軽音部
ええ
Indeed.
All right, Budokan, here we come!
夢は武道館ライブ
ええッ？
By the time we graduate!
卒業までに
ええ～ッ
I'm sorry. That's all I can play right now.
ごめん まだ これしか弾けない
I guess I should learn a lot more before I try playing with an amp.
アンプで音をならすのは もう少ししてからだね
Ah, be careful!
あッ 危ない！
Huh?
That's what happens when you pull off the guitar cord before you turn the amp all the way down.
アンプのボリューム下げる前にコード抜くと
そうなっちゃうんだよ…
You should've said something sooner...
はッ 早く言って…
Sign: 1065 days until the live performance at the Budokan?!
Please
don't say
you are
lazy,
Please don't say“You are lazy”
because
you are
actually
crazy
だって本当はcrazy
The swans
are actually
白鳥達はそう　見えないところでバタ足するんです
kicking their legs
hard out
of sight
Being true and sincere to my instincts,
I accept that I'll
be tossed around
本能に従順 忠実　翻弄も重々承知
The path ahead looks bright
前途洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
That's why I
take rests
sometimes
近道あればそれが王道　はしょれる翼もあれば上等
If there's a shortcut,
it's the best route
If I have wings to use, then it'll be the best
Crap, I broke a nail!
I'll fix it with glue
ヤバ 爪割れた　グルーで補修した
That's enough to give me
a sense of achievement
それだけでなんか達成感
大事なのは自分　かわいがること
What's important is to take good care of yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ　他人も愛せない
If you can't love yourself, then you can't love someone else
Please
don't
say
you
are
Please don't say“You are lazy”
because
you
are
actually
だって本当はcrazy
Skilled
hawks
能ある鷹はそう　見えないとこにピック隠すんです
hide their talons
out of sight
I try to use my imagination,
想像に一生懸命　現実は絶体絶命
but reality is a bitch
I'm still just learning,
発展途中だし…だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
so I'll be out of pitch sometimes
Next Episode
えッ 中間テスト!?
Ah! We've got midterm exams?!
Is that a chord too?
それも コード？
I don't get it, Yui. Why didn't you study?
何で勉強しなかったのさ
Oh, I really had planned to, but I...
いや～ しようと思ったんだけれど
Come on, when you study for a test, don't you ever end up fixating on everything but studying?
なんか 試験勉強中ってさ
勉強以外のことに 集中できたりしない？
Oh, look at that! It's sweet bean jelly!
今日は ようかん～
Special Training!